<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">
  <a name="scope">  </a>
	<p>
    Este documento é um  FHIR Implementation Guide. Contem especificações desenvolvidas pela comunidade HL7 e pela SPMS para o uso de FHIR.
   </p>
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
	<strong> Este documento e artefactos estão sob desenvolvimento.</strong>
	Este conteúdo é para efeitos demonstrativos apenas.
	</blockquote>
	<p> </p>
  <h3>Conteúdo</h3> <a name="content"> </a>
	<p/>

<p>Esta publicação contém as especificações técnicas sobre a Gestão de Medicação PEMH</p>
<p></p>
<p>Existe também uma introdução e motivação para esta especificação.</p>
<p></p>

<a name="navigation"> </a>
<p>O menu no topo permite uma navegação rápida entre diferentes secções e o <a href="toc.html">Índice</a> contém uma listagem do conteudo total deste Implementation Guide. </p>
<p></p>
	<a name="ip"> </a>
	<h3>Intellectual Property Considerations</h3>
	<p>
    While this implementation guide and the underlying FHIR are licensed as public domain, this guide includes examples making use of terminologies such 
    as LOINC, SNOMED CT and others which have more restrictive licensing requirements. Implementers should make themselves familiar with licensing and 
    any other constraints of terminologies, questionnaires, and other components used as part of their implementation process. In some cases, 
    licensing requirements may limit the systems that data captured using certain questionnaires may be shared with.
  </p>

	<a name="disclaimer"> </a>
	<h3>Disclaimer</h3>
	<p>
    The specification herewith documented is a demo working specification, and may not be used for any implementation purposes. 
    This draft is provided without warranty of completeness or consistency, and the official publication supersedes this draft.
    No liability can be inferred from the use or misuse of this specification, or its consequences.
  </p>
</div>